<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mario&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mario&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:48:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Hugo to Firebase</title>
      <link>/deploy-hugo-to-firebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:48:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/deploy-hugo-to-firebase/</guid>
      <description>Deploying website with Hugo. This is actualy very easy.
From the project root directory, run:
hugo -D This will populate the /public directory with updated content.
Now the app is ready to be deployed to Firebase.
Deploying to Firebase Create a project within a firebase console, and in the hosting section, follow the instruction to set up project name, etc&amp;hellip;
Then, from the console , project root directory run:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo in Depth Part 2</title>
      <link>/hugo-in-depth-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 23:33:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-in-depth-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Archetypes In archetypes/default.md - data can be inserted here to display on any page created by hugo. If .md file created here will corespond with directory within the content folder, any posts created will have coresponding data inserted.
archetypes/ default.md directory1.md content/ page1.md directory1/ page2.md page3.md Here ⤴ , page2 will have data from directory1.md file and the rest of the files (page1, page3) will get its data from default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo in Depth Part 1</title>
      <link>/hugo-in-depth-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 21:04:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-in-depth-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Install latest version Google Hugo releases page on github. Download latest release and follow the steps to install based on the OS.
Directory structure Start new project in desired directory with
hugo new site sitename Folders   Archetypes
 Define content in the website    content
 Place where all website content goes (posts, etc&amp;hellip;)    data
 Kind of like database. All data goes there (like json files)    layouts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 17:23:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is fast, Hugo is flexible, Hugo is simple Hugo is not about configuration and fancy styling like lot of Javascript libraries, Hugo is about content. Because quality content is still a king. And always will be.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with Hugo.
To Install Hugo To install Hugo on macOS, from your terminal run
brew install hugo For Windows and Linux, check the official installation guide.
Once Hugo is installed, you create a Hugo site by running in terminal</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>